<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<fpdoc-descriptions><package name="lazbbcomponents"><module name="lazbbcontrols">

    <element name="TColorPicker"><short>Colors choice similar to Components inspector (Colors combo box plus colors dialog button)</short><descr>Base colors, and their identifiers cannot be changed.<br/>
  Selected text cannot be edited. To change the selected color, use the colors dialog
  or paste a color with the popup menu. An invalid color is ignored.<br/>
  Selected colours not in base colours are added at the end of the list.<br/>
  Like base combo box, component height is related to the items height.<br/>
  The colors dialog is localized by the operating system.
</descr>
      </element><element name="TColorPicker.ItemHeight"><short>The default height of an item in the drop-down for the control.</short><descr>Like base combo box, component height is related to the items height.
</descr>
      </element><element name="TColorPicker.ItemWidth"><short>The minimum width of the items in the drop-down list.</short><descr>The minimum width of the items in the drop-down list.
</descr>
      </element><element name="TColorPicker.MnuCopyCaption"><short>"Copy" menu item to copy the selected color to the clipboard</short>
      </element><element name="TColorPicker.MnuPasteCaption"><short>"Paste" menu item to paste the selected color from the clipboard</short>
      </element><element name="TColorPicker.Color"><short>Default selected color.</short><descr>Thiw is not the component color, but the default color selected and returned by the component.
</descr>
      </element><element name="TCheckBoxX"><short>Multifunction check box: colored square, cross, check mark, image.</short><descr>The checkbox can be customized: color, type of check, image...
</descr>
      </element><element name="TCheckBoxX.AllowGrayed"><short>Mimics the visual of disabled state.</short><descr>The contro; is not disabled. The user can use the component évents to customize the behaviour in this mode.
</descr>
      </element><element name="TCheckBoxX.CheckBoxType"><short>Type of check on the box</short><descr>cbBMP: Image<br/>
cbBullet: Bullet<br/>
cbCross: Cross (similar to classic checkbox)<br/>
cbDiamond: Diamond<br/>
cbMark: Mark<br/>
cbRect: empty;



</descr>
      </element><element name="TCheckBoxX.CheckColor"><short>check square color</short>
      </element><element name="TCheckBoxX.State"><short>Checkbox state </short><descr>cbChecked; checked state<br/>
cbUnchecked: unchecked state<br/>
cbGrayed: Grayed state
</descr>
      </element><element name="TTitlePanel"><short>Panel with a title like a GroupBox. Can change border color and title alignment</short><descr>Mimics a groupbox with a tile alignment property and customizable border line and color
</descr>
      </element><element name="TTitlePanel.BorderLine"><short>Box line type</short><descr>bsSingle: solid border<br/>
bsNone: No border line
</descr>
      </element><element name="TTitlePanel.BorderColor"><short>Color of the box border</short>
      </element><element name="TSignalMeter"><short>More responsive progress bar</short><descr>As it is more respopnsive than classic progress bar, the componzent can be used to show siognal leveles in real time.
</descr>
      </element>
    </module>
  </package>
</fpdoc-descriptions>
